tripaura.com 2013-12-08

# Privacy Policy

TripAura Travel International Inc is committed to respecting your privacy. We have designed our websites and booking engines so that you may visit them without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information, unless you opt to do so. Once you opt to provide personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card number), it will only be used to support your customer relationship with us and for our own internal purposes, including marketing and research, customization of our websites and improving the content of our websites.

This Online Privacy Statement regarding the privacy of the information you provide online covers the following main areas: Awareness, What we Collect, Information Sharing, Choice, Access & Accuracy, Security, Oversight, and Right to Change.

 **Awareness**

TripAura Travel International Inc provides this Online Privacy Statement to inform you about our privacy policy and the practices and choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice may be accessed from any area ofÂ  TripAura Travel International Inc websites and our online proprietary booking engines.

What we collect

When making a reservation:

When you make a reservation online or by phone through our customer support center, you will be asked for your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and credit card information. This information is used to contact you for customer service, to guaranty your reservation with our travel suppliers and/or to bill you for your travel purchase. We may also ask you for other personal information, such as your frequent traveler numbers. During the booking process you can choose not to receive our newsletter or travel reminders by unchecking the appropriate boxes on the online form. Thereafter, if you would rather not receive them, please click on the "unsubscribe" link or follow the instructions in each e-mail message.

 **Third-party vendors:**

Some of TripAura Travel International Inc online booking engines are powered by third-party vendors. You should note that these vendors may have privacy policies and practices that differ from those of TripAura Travel International Inc. We strongly encourage you to read the privacy policies of these vendors when using their websites.

 **E-Postcards:**

TripAura Travel International Inc provides electronic postcards cards via our websites and our affiliate websites for you to send to a friend. We store the e-mail address of all recipients, the message you want to send and the URL for locating the greeting card. We do not sell, distribute, or license in anyway the use of recipient e-mail addresses. We use them solely for the purposes of notifying recipients on your behalf that a card is waiting for them at the designated URL. After 30 days, all information pertaining to your postcard is deleted.

 **About Cookies  
**  
Many websites, including those owned by TripAura Travel International Inc use cookie technology to help users navigate efficiently. The cookie is a small text file that resides on your hard drive. From time to time, our site(s) will request the cookie from your browser so that we can retrieve the stored information. This allows you to avoid making the same selections over and over again. TripAura Travel International Inc does not use cookies to store personal information, such as credit-card numbers.

An example of how cookies are used is as follows: When you conduct a search using our booking engine for hotels in Orlando, a cookie will be set recording the city of Orlando as the parameter of your search. When you return to the search form to narrow or change your search, Orlando will automatically be entered into the city field in the search form.

Please note that with most browsers, a user can set the preferences to show a warning each time a cookie request is received. You can also usually set the browser not to accept cookies at all. However, to make your experience using our booking engines as convenient as possible, we suggest that you allow your browser to accept cookies.

 **Information Sharing**

TripAura Travel International Inc will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other third-party vendors that are acting to complete reservation services. We do not knowingly permit the site to be used by any person under the age of eighteen and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children (meaning those younger than thirteen years of age). We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities.

 **Choice**

TripAura Travel International Inc will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the purposes described above without letting you know and offering you a choice. Please be aware that our website and those of our affiliates may contain links to other websites, and that the privacy practices of these other websites may differ from those of TripAura Travel International Inc. This Online Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all other websites you visit.

 **Access & Accuracy**

TripAura Travel International Inc strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate. We make every effort to provide you with online access to your registration data so that you may update or correct your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections to your user account.

 **Security**

TripAura Travel International Inc is committed to protecting the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information.

 **Oversight**

If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, e-mail:  

Your use of our website is subject to our User Agreement.

 **Right to Change**

We review our Privacy Policy from time to time, and may make changes to the policy pursuant to such review. Please periodically review this page to make sure you have the current version. Regardless of changes, we will abide by the privacy practices described to you in this Privacy Policy at the time you provided us with your personal information. The foregoing Privacy Policy was last updated on April 12, 2011.
